greencart.in 2014-11-24

# Greencart.in - Offers Online Fresh Fruits, Vegetables & Gourmet

Welcome to Greencart. Greencart.in ('website','Web Site','site','we','us','our') is committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer (you,your,user) information privacy. PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PRIVACY POLICY and _USER TERMS AND CONDITIONS_ CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.   
By accepting the Privacy Policy and the " _User Terms and Conditions_ ", you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the " _User Terms and Conditions_ ". This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance in registration for new registering users, and is otherwise effective on **1 January 2013** for all users.  
Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please bookmark this page and periodically review this policy. Of course, you may always submit concerns regarding our Privacy Policy via email to _Contact us_. 

## **Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, delivery address and birth date.) from you when you set up a free account with Greencart.in. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as placing an order) do require registration.  
From time to time we may add or enhance services available on Greencart.in site. To the extent these services are provided, and used by you, we will use the information you provide to facilitate the service requested. For example, if you email us or call upon us with a question we will use your email address, name, nature of the question, etc. to respond to your question. We may also store such information to assist us in making the site the better and easier to use.

## **Safeguard to protect your personal information**

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access. ** ** All data on the Greencart.in site is Comodo positive SSL secured. Further all the payments on the Greencart.in site is Verisign SSL secured. You may notice that through the use of "https:" instead of "http:" url for _https://www.Greencart.in_ .

This means all personal information you provide to Greencart.in is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. 

Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords, and your Greencart.in site membership account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you are online.

## **Optional Online Surveys**

Greencart.in values opinions and comments from members, so we frequently conduct online surveys. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information is aggregated, and used to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in--and to display content according to your preferences. 

## **Automatic Logging of Session Data**

We automatically log generic information about your computer connection to the Internet, which we call "session data", that is anonymous and not linked to any personal information. Session data consists of things such as IP address, operating system and type of browser software being used and the activities conducted by the user while on Greencart.in site. An IP address is a number that lets computers attached to the internet, such as our web servers, know where to send data back to the user, such as the pages of the site the user wishes to view. 

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

## **Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a Web server to a Web browser, which enables to collect information from the browser. We also use cookies to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session. Cookies can also help us provide information that is targeted to your interests. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on the Site and you may be required to re-enter your password more frequently during a session.

Greencart.in places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer hard drive. Greencart.in cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.

## **Use of Demographic and Profile Data**

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you through your email-address registered with us. We use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms and conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection. 

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users activity on our website. 

## **Choice/Opt-Out/Unsubscribe from Promotions**

As a Greencart.in site member you will also occasionally receive updates from us about Product or Services & Promotional Offers, special offers via your Email id registered with us. However, you may choose at any time to no longer receive these types of e - mail messages. Please see our  _How-to-Unsubscribe_ for details.

## **Sharing of personal information**

When you register or buy a product or service through Greencart.in, we use non - personally identifiable information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Greencart.in Site. We may provide anonymous statistical information based on this data to suppliers, advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We may also use such aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their web sites. Occasionally, Greencart.in will hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market - research surveys and contest - entry processing and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information we provide to such third parties is protected by a confidentiality agreement and is to be used solely for completing the specific project.

## **Links to Other Sites**

Greencart.in site contains links to other web sites. We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information about your visits to their links and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another web site for which Greencart.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from this Privacy Policy.

## **Other**

In addition to the circumstances described above, Greencart.in may disclose the Greencart.in site member information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Greencart.in or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. In addition, if Greencart.in or substantially all of its assets are acquired, our customer information will most likely also be transferred in connection with such acquisition 

## **Disclaimer**

The information contained in this Web Site is only for general information about Greencart.in, and the services that they offer and is not in any way binding on Greencart.in. It does not constitute advice and should not be relied upon in making or refraining from making any decision.

 Greencart.in hereby excludes any warranty (either expressed or implied) as to the correctness, completeness, timeliness, accuracy, fitness for a particular purpose of the Web Site or any of its contents.

By accessing this Web Site you agree that Greencart.in will not be liable for any direct or indirect or consequential loss, damages or compensation arising from the use of the information and material contained in this Web Site or from your access of other material on the internet via web links for this Web Site.
